(Penny:)It's getting
kind of cheesy, Leonard.
(Sheldon:)Huh?
(Leonard:)If you think that's
cheesy, buckle up.
(Leonard:)Penny Hofstadter,
(Leonard:)will you please
stay married to me?
(Penny:)Oh, damn it, you topped it.
(Penny:)Should we go to the bedroom
and make this marriage official?
Yes, please!
Okay!
(Penny:)Sheldon, I can't believe
you got us a wedding gift.
(Penny:)I don't know
why you're so surprised.
I watch movies;
I see what people do.
(Leonard:)What is this?
(Sheldon:)Plane tickets
and hotel reservations
(Sheldon:)for a weekend away
in San Francisco.
Oh!
Wow!
That's so great!
(Sheldon:)Yeah, there's Fisherman's Wharf
and Alcatraz and cable cars.
(Sheldon:)We're gonna have so much fun.
(knocking on door)
(Penny:)We?
(Sheldon:)Is there a problem?
Oh, no, no!
I just, I said, "Whee!"
(Amy(at door):)How dare you go on the Internet
and say mean things about me
(Amy(at door):)and compare my genitalia
to part of Czechoslovakia?!
(Sheldon:)You saw through that one,
did you?
(Penny:)I don't know
what you were thinking,
but take the video down now!
(Sheldon:)She watched it.
(Sheldon:)I'm gonna get that girl back.
AMY: I only watched it
because you e-mailed it to me
with the subject line:
"This is gonna make you mad"!
(Sheldon:)She was listening through
the door. She wants me.